Engine reasonably
yeah
I'm doing it.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
Today is the music video shooting for After School Gyutto!
yay!
Well, it's been a long time since I've been in
It's more like school
We are, aren't we?
Yup.
Yeah.
It's been a while.
Really.
We're graduating.
It feels nostalgic.
Yeah.
Seeing this view...
Heh.
We're shooting a music video at school, too.
It's the first time for me to do a cause.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It was really nostalgic.
A little bit.
I'm trying to get that back, too.
Get it back? What?
Get it back?
The feeling.
Yeah.
The feeling of school.
Yes, that's right.
Get a sense of that, too.
Yes.
A little bit.
I want to do my best.
I'll do my best.
I haven't filmed it yet.
I haven't done it yet.
I'm really...
From now on.
Just a little while longer.
It's about to start.
Okay.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll do my best.
Well, that was fun. You're tired.
Ooh! Cool!
Who's going?
Masai will definitely be there.
Okay, I'll go.
I'll go then.
Okay.
After that...
like this
and then like this
Kaito Miyachika I'm doing it like this.
Kawashima: No, no, no, no, no.
Kawashima, Ryoza, come running.
Kaito Miyachika, come running.
Kaito Miyachika, come on.
Kaito, ask me what we're having for breakfast.
Kawashima, go!
Kaito, what's for breakfast?
Kawashima: Takanori took it first.
Kawashima And then I joined him.
Kaito Miyachika, it's tough.
Kawashima, what's going on?
Kaito Miyachika, it's hard.
Kawashima... I'll do it.
Kaito Miyachika, you're in.
Kawashima, okay.
Kaito Miyachika, okay.
Kawashima Okay.
Kaito Miyachika, let's go!
Kaito Miyachika, let's go.
One more test. Please do it.
Start!
Wow, today's social studies class was really boring.
Oh, first!
OK. Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go live.
OK, then.
Please.
Okay, thank you.
All right, let's get started.
Well, today's social was just bad.
Really bad.
I'm working in the morning.
Cut, cut, cut.
What are you doing?
I've been coming here all day.
I don't know why.
Thanks for your help.
Bat. OK.
OK, thank you.
Yes, OK, thank you.
Yes, so today we're shooting the music video for After School Gyutto.
Well, it feels like after school, doesn't it?
I'm tired because I'm tired because I'm tired because I'm tired because I'm tired.
Well, we've just finished the first cut.
And they said, "Okay, you can do one cut, one cut.
Thank you very much.
As expected...
I used a film camera this time.
I don't mean to say that I put my heart and soul into every shot, but...
I have to take care of each shot one by one.
You can't take many shots.
Once I say I'm sorry, that's it.
There's a guy who made a terrible mistake.
What?
Tell us more.
Please come by.
Well, just so you know, ladies and gentlemen, this is all part of the act.
Kin was acting, too.
Ko-chan was acting too.
Takanori, of course.
It was good, it was good.
Masaya was great!
Thank you very much.
You were great.
Of course I did.
Of course you did.
Many times.
I said... to all of you...
I said, "Hey, what are you doing?
Next to me, it's normal.
If it was the other way around, I'd say the line again.
You don't have to say it like a parrot.
Yes, yes, yes.
Next to me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I can't think.
Cuz I was wondering.
It's a parrot, not a parakeet.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I did it!
So, as you can see... today, too...
I'm going to do my best to shoot the music video for the advertisement...I will do my best to shoot the music video for the ad.
Yes, sir.
Let's do our best.
Well, we've only just started.
Let's start here.
You're right, I'm not a parrot.
I'm a parrot now.
Let's do our best for the day.
Okay, everyone.
Vogel.
Kinky, kinky, kinky, kinky.
Whoa!
What are you doing, cuz?
Hey, Jayne.
It's a big gym when you travel, isn't it?
We didn't have a gym this big at school.
And the location is so nice.
It's right on the ocean.
It's so open!
Someone is recording, right?
I'm not the voice today. It's someone else's voice.
Who's that? Who's that?
Who's that?
I think I know who it is.
What? Birdcage?
Is it a birdcage?
Is the birdcage on?
Yes, sir.
You want to do that one?
That one?
Yes, sir.
One, two, three.
He's so desperate.
He's gonna be so desperate.
He's slow, but he looks desperate.
There he is.
There she is at recess.
She's going to cry in two minutes.
Isn't your hay fever getting worse?
I've been blowing my nose so much because of hay fever.
Don't worry about it.
I'm going to work hard after school.
Today's shoot was really fun.
I mean, so far everything is okay. We've just finished the school scene.
All that's left is the cut scene.
I hope you enjoy the music video.
I think it's going to be pretty emotional.
Please look forward to it.
I'm still working on the photos.
Video?
Ha-ha-ha.
Nice half
The good half
The better half
The better half.
Wait a minute.
One, one, one.
The one that resonated.
Matsukura Okay, okay, okay.
I don't need that.
I don't want that one. It's a failure.
Matsukura, hehehe
Matsukura, one by one
Matsukura I'm looking at you, I'm looking at you
Matsukura, bigger and bigger! Nakamura, cry!
Matsukura Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Matsukura, bigger and bigger
No, no, no, not that...
Matsukura, cry!
Matsukura, look over here!
Matsukura Heh heh heh heh
Matsukura Okay, okay, Nakamura Wow, great!
Nakamura I used it and quit
Nakamura I lived
Matsukura, cry
Nakamura, that's the biggest one
Matsukura I'm a little tired
Matsukura I'm going to cry in March
Matsukura No, you're crying now
But it's a midnight stop.
It's still midnight.
I'm looking good in the shadows.
Oh, shadows.
Okay, let's go to the show.
All right, let's go!
Oooooooooooh!
Staff, I thought you were leaving.
The sound of a camera shutter.
Is that you and me?
Oh no, no, no, no!
I'm with someone.
I'm with someone
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Maybe I shouldn't talk to him.
Traveler's block.
Locals.
Good morning.
Oh, no.
Are they starting a fight? Could it be...
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, there you are.
That's funny.
Quick! Quick!
The way he runs.
Quick!
I didn't know there was a hill up there.
Downhill
It's a mountain turtle.
You know what?
It's coming right at us.
I can't keep up.
You sure you don't want us to go alone? More?
I thought I was supposed to be cheering you on.
I'm cheering you on. I want you to water the canaries and stuff.
Top two, right?
Top two right there.
Here we go!
How do you run?
Absolutely no form.
That's no way to run!
Come on!
You can't run like that.
Thank you.
Water, water, water.
Invisible wall
You'll hit a good wall.
This isn't good, is it?
What?
No, I mean...
It's the view from the hallway.
It's great.
Isn't that Mt. Fuji? Hey, doggy.
Oh, is that Kumu?
Kumu.
Let's just call anything Mt. Fuji if we can find a tall enough mountain.
Here, take a peek.
Ugh, I can't!
Oh, no.
Go for it!
Yeah, sure.
How much?
This way?This way?
Oklah, this much?
That's it?
Gaga, gaga, gaga, gaga.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Over the top.
Okay... let's get into it... let's get into it...
Whoo-hoo.
♪♪
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm taking on a challenge right now that I should never take on.
Hey, Birds.
Whoo-hoo!
Whew... boo-boo... boo-boo...
Boat, boat, boat
Whoo-hoo-hoo...
Hey, don't say "Cars" like you do "Bars".
Hey, Birds!
Okay, let's get to work.
Sound, please.
Music!
Music.
Is this a school?
No, it's not.
It's like...
We have all kinds of school goods.
What's that?
Blackboard-colored.
It's nice, isn't it?
Blackboard color.
I see.
Like a classroom.
Ta-da!
Here we go.
This is a new outfit.
It's like an after-school get-together.
They're all wearing uniforms.
It's like a remake of the dressing room.
It's so cute and my favorite!
My favorite point is the pearl necklace.
and the green innerwear.
my member's color green or green.
I guess that's about it.
There are more music videos to come, so I'll do my best!
Now, let's go to the main event, Jonahs!
Please go as soon as possible.
When I hear the word "first" and then I just put it out, it's too much like a "gwin", isn't it?
Oh, I understand.
Let's do it. I'll be on the show.
Thank you for your hard work.
Photo.
Ok.
Yes, good work.
We will bake the leek dough.
Only red meat and yolk.
Zoro Mumumumu
When it is nicely baked and done, it is done!
Matsukura Do it again, 10 seconds.
Matsukura 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 5
Yoshizawa You have good back muscles. Your back muscles are the most determined.
Miyachika, this is bad.
Yoshizawa Everything is different!
〜BGM
Hello everyone!
The game is on me.
It's a Voiceme craft!
This is Sakura Original
Today is the original issue
We're shooting a music video.
Already, we're in the final stages.
How are you feeling? How do you feel now?
We're in the final stages.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I can remember those memories of school and so on.
I haven't finished everything yet.
I'm going to do my best.
Let's go for it!
Let's go!
You and me, we're gonna pop
♪ Love, let's connect ♪
♪ Now it seems there's no lie ♪
# Tomorrow I'll never lose
Someday my heart
♪ Will fall in the air ♪
Thank you for watching.
Hello! The gain is yours!
Yes! So this time, we finished shooting the music video for After School Gyutto!
Yes! Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work!
You're tired, aren't you?
Yes, sir!
Well, it was really good this time.
I especially liked the image cut.
I thought the classroom set was really nice.
I thought it was really nice.
What do you think?
I'm glad I got to go to the actual school.
And the school building.
Yes, it was.
For the older students, it's been a long time since they've seen a classroom.
For the older ones, it's been a long time since they've seen a classroom.
It was really nice.
How's it going? Kanagawa?
No, but it was nice to dance something I've never danced before.
I wanted to ask you something.
It's true.
It doesn't happen in real life.
I'm really looking forward to seeing the choreography.
That's for sure
What do you think, Yossan?
Yes, can I show you something?
Yes, I do.
The highlight is the second chorus.
Jun's singing.
You can see his foot.
That's my foot.
That's the highlight.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Now, outside, please pay attention to the highlight.
Jun, please look forward to the video.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
Bye bye!
Go home!